# KAMAL SHARMA

## Professional Summary

Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at Gujarat Technological University in the last three years. I am pursuing B.E degree from Mahavir Swami College of Engineering and Technology and has worked as an intern with several startups and companies in the field of Web Development and Data Science.

## Employment history

Data Science Intern, Dev Town (Skill Safari).

Dec. 2021 - Present

Python for ML/Al Intern, Elite Techno Groups.

Aug. 2021 - Sep. 2021

Full Stack Development Intern, Skill Safari.

May. 2021 - Jun. 2021

Front-End Developer Intern, Skill Safari.

Aug. 2020 - Nov. 2020

#### Education

Mahavir Swami College of Engineering and Technology, Surat, Gujarat

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engg., Present

Divine Child High School, Surat, Gujarat

HSC, May. 2019

Divine Child High School, Surat, Gujarat

SSC, May. 2017

#### Personal info

Phone:

+91 9724835275

Email:

kamal5201ks@gmail.com

Address:

D-08, 330, Raj Abhishek City Homes, Sachin, Surat, 394230 (IN)

Languages

**English** 

Hindi

Gujarati

Skills

C++

Java

**Python** 

**Back-End Development** 

Front-End Development

**Data Science**